Guide to the Ed Smith Papers 1974-2005 (Bulk 1978-2004) MSS.177
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series II: Correspondence and Subject Series
  - Gerstler, Amy, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 151)
  - Gerstler, Amy [additional material (pair of cufflinks) separated to oversize box], 1984 (Box 5, Folder 152, Box 10)
  - Gerstler, Amy, 1985-1989, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 153)
  - Gerstler, Amy [notes and poems], undated (Box 5, Folder 154)
  - Gerstler, Amy [miscellaneous - includes photograph], undated (Box 5, Folder 155)
  - Geza X [a (found?) notebook], 1983 (Box 5, Folder 156)
  - Grace [includes photographs][-see also oversize], undated (Box 5, Folder 157, Box 10)
  - Guest List 1978 (Box 5, Folder 158)
  - Hall, Steven [includes slides] [-see also oversize], 1983-1984 (Box 5, Folder 159, Box 10)
  - Hall, Steven [includes photograph], 1985-1991 (Box 5, Folder 160)
  - Hall, Steven, undated (Box 5, Folder 161)
  - Highlights [magazine], 1988, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 162)
  - [High School and College], 1974-1975, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 163)
  - Holly, John, undated (Box 5, Folder 164)
  - Hollywood Memorial Park, undated (Box 5, Folder 165)
  - [Invitation Cards] [includes Danceteria, Oranges/Sardines, Piezo Electric, others], 1979-1996, undated (Box 5, Folder 166)
  - Jessica [Goin], 1983-1986 (Box 5, Folder 167)
  - Jessica [Goin] [includes photographs], 1987-1989, undated (Box 5, Folder 168)
  - Johnson, Martha [includes photographs][-see also oversize], 1985-1987, undated (Box 5, Folder 169, Box 10)
  - "L.A. Men", 1982 (Box 5, Folder 170)
  - Lay, Carol [drawings], undated (Box 5, Folder 171)
  - Local 47, 1978-1979 (Box 5, Folder 172)
  - Los Angeles, County of, Department of Health Services, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 173)
  - MAC [includes photographs][additional material (Black Sabbath poster) separated to oversize box, 1984-1987, undated (Box 5, Folder 174, Box 10)
  - [Mailing List and Phone List], undated (Box 5, Folder 175)
  - Mary [Williams] [includes photographs], 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 176)
  - Mary [Williams] [includes photographs], 1986 (Box 5, Folder 177)
  - Mary [Williams], 1986-1989 (bulk 1986) (Box 5, Folder 178)
  - Mary [Williams] [includes photographs and negatives][additional materials (drawings) separated to oversize box], undated (Box 5, Folder 179, Box 10)
  - Mary [Williams] [Printed materials], 1959-1986 (Box 5, Folder 180)
  - Melody [Mendell], 1988 (Box 5, Folder 181)
  - [Miscellaneous Correspondence] [Gail Kaszynski, Arrow, Kathy, Benjamin Weissman, Barbara Karpp, Susan Lash, Jim, Kim Rosenfield, Elizabeth Delude, Anne, Courtney, Jane DeLynn, Mike Wallace], 1981-2001 (Box 5, Folder 182)
  - [Miscellaneous Materials Found Inside Books and Periodicals], 1987-2001, undated (Box 5, Folder 183)
  - [Miscellaneous Materials Saved by Ed Smith] [including, among other items, mental health survey, ticket stubs, religious pamphlets, menu, funeral booklet, Tim Miller's birth certificate][-see also oversize], 1982, 1984, undated (Box 5, Folder 184, Box 10)
  - Pat [Williams], 1986-1989 (Box 5, Folder 185)
  - Pearce, Celia, 1983-1984 (Box 6, Folder 186)
  - Pearce, Celia [includes photographs], 1985-1990, undated (Box 6, Folder 187)
  - [Photographs] [includes group photos of L.A. poets], undated (Box 6, Folder 188)
  - Photos 2 [this is a folder created and named by Ed Smith, and it also includes postcards], undated (Box 6, Folder 189)
  - Picken, Miranda, 1981-1991 (Box 6, Folder 190)
  - Quantum Semantics, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 191)
  - Rosetta, 1980-1981, undated (Box 6, Folder 192)
  - Sheldrake, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 193)
  - Smith vs. Anti-Club, 1982-1985 (Box 6, Folder 194)
  - Smith vs. Anti-Club, 1987-1988 (Box 6, Folder 195)
  - Souvenirs 1979 [ticket stubs] (Box 6, Folder 196)
  - Sumie, 1986, undated (Box 6, Folder 197)
  - Suzanne [Goin][-see also oversize], 1983-1985 (Box 6, Folder 198, Box 10)
  - Suzanne [Goin], 1986-1991, undated (Box 6, Folder 199)
  - Tiger [pet] [includes photographs], 1987-1989, undated (Box 6, Folder 200)
  - Title House, 1987-1995, undated (Box 6, Folder 201)
  - [Typesetting Work][-see also oversize], 1982-1985 (Box 6, Folder 202, Box 10)
  - Velazquez, Gerardo, 1979-1981, undated (Box 6, Folder 203)
  - [Robert Williams] [Invitations to shows at Psychedelic Solution and La Luz de Jesus], 1987-1994 (Box 6, Folder 204)
  - Yarbrough, Rik [includes photographs], undated (Box 6, Folder 205)
- Series III: Drafts, Production Materials, Final Published Work
  This series consists of published copies of Smith's books and articles, production material related to Tim's Bunnies, and draft material, including drafts by other writers. It is arranged chronologically.
  - Flat Disk Newsletter (3 poems by Ed Smith), [1982] (Box 7, Folder 206)
  - Fantasyworld, published version, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 207)
  - Typed Prose: "A Story" and a fragment, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 208)
  - Barney no. 4, "Ponderous Execution" by Ed Smith, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 209)
  - Journalism for the L.A. Reader - drafts and final versions, 1984, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 210)
  - Draft interviews of Ingrid Baumgart and Jim Isserman for Shiny, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 211)
  - Poetry Loves Poetry, published collection of poems and photographs of poets, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 212)
  - Draft article about Ed Smith, [1985] (Box 7, Folder 213)
  - cut-up poetry by Ed Smith, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 214)
  - Shiny International, no. 1, Ed Smith interviews Jim Isserman, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 215)
  - Mirage, no. 2, 3 poems by Ed Smith, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 216)
  - Typed Prose: "Icelandic Women and Fish" and "Tonga: the Abode of Love" by Ed Smith, [1986] (Box 7, Folder 217)
  - Shiny International, no. 2, 2 poems by Ed Smith, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 218)
  - Shiny International, no. 3, 3 poems by Ed Smith, and Ed Smith interviews Mike Kelley, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 219)
  - Cooper, Dennis: manuscript of Closer, [1987 or 1988] (finished book published 1989) (Box 7, Folder 220)
  - Friedman, Michael: draft of On My Way to See You, [1987?] (Box 7, Folder 221)
  - Friedman, Michael: draft of Binoculars, [1988?] (Box 7, Folder 222)
  - Tim's Bunnies Production Materials, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 223)
  - Tim's Bunnies Production Materials, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 224)
  - Tim's Bunnies Production Materials, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 225)
  - Tim's Bunnies Production Materials, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 226)
  - Tim's Bunnies, final published version, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 227)
  - B City, no. 5, 2 poems by Ed Smith, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 228)
  - Beyond Baroque typesetting work, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 229)
  - Santa Monica Review, vol. 2, no. 1, 2 poems by Ed Smith, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 230)
  - Poems written on acetate, projected during reading, undated [1980's] (Box 7, Folder 231)
  - Roman Beauty/Excelsior! by Ed Smith, undated [1980's] (Box 7, Folder 232)
  - Ed Smith interviews Chris Burden, drafts and final version in Shiny no. 5, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 233)
  - Shiny International, no. 6: Ed Smith is "West Coast Editor", 1991 (Box 7, Folder 234)
  - Hall, Steven: Black Watch Production Materials, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 235)
  - Interview of Ed Smith for Aeon Electron, 31 January 2005 (Box 7, Folder 236)
  - Fragments of a long manuscript by Ed Smith, undated (Box 7, Folder 237)
  - "Susan #1" (microcassette), undated (Box 7, Folder 238)
- Series IV: Printed Materials
  Series IV, Printed Materials, consists of four subseries of materials collected by Ed Smith: subseries A is books arranged alphabetically by author, subseries B consists of periodicals arranged alphabetically by title, subseries C contains catalogs for art shows, arranged chronologically, and subseries D is miscellaneous printed materials, arranged chronologically. Other books and periodicals owned by Ed Smith have been separated out and moved to the stacks of the Fales Downtown Collection.
  - Subseries A: monographs
    - Abbot, Steve: Skinny Trip to a Far Place, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 238)
    - Aguayo, Rafael: Dr. Deming, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 239)
    - Aguayo, Rafael: The MetaKnowledge Advantage, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 240)
    - Britton, Donald: Italy (inscribed), 1981 (Box 8, Folder 241)
    - Brownstein, Michaeal: Highway to the Sky, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 242)
    - Brownstein, Michael: Oracle Night, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 243)
    - Cooper, Dennis: Closer, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 244)
    - Cooper, Dennis (editor): Coming Attractions: An Anthology of American Poets in Their Twenties, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 245)
    - Cooper, Dennis: Guide (inscribed), 1997 (Box 8, Folder 246)
    - Cooper, Dennis: He Cried (inscribed), 1984 (Box 8, Folder 247)
    - Cooper, Dennis: Safe, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 248)
    - Cooper, Dennis: The Tenderness of the Wolves, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 249)
    - Deifik, Kenneth: The Focus Puller (inscribed), 1983 (Box 8, Folder 250)
    - Dlugos, Tim: Entre Nous, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 251)
    - Dlugos, Tim: A Fast Life, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 252)
    - Flanagan, Bob: Fuck Journal, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 253)
    - Flanagan, Bob: Slave Sonnets (inscribed), 1986 (Box 8, Folder 254)
    - Flanagan, Bob and Trinidad, David: A Taste of Honey (inscribed), 1990 (Box 8, Folder 255)
    - Flanagan, Bob: The Wedding of Everything (inscribed), 1983 (Box 8, Folder 256)
    - Friedman, Michael: Distinctive Belt (inscribed), 1985 (Box 8, Folder 257)
    - Gerstler,Amy: Bitter Angel, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 258)
    - Gerstler, Amy: Christy's Alpine Inn, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 259)
    - Gerstler, Amy: Crown of Weeds, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 260)
    - Gerstler, Amy: Martine's Mouth, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 261)
    - Gerstler, Amy: Medicine, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 262)
    - Gerstler, Amy: Nerve Storm, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 263)
    - Gerstler, Amy: The True Bride, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 264)
    - Gerstler, Amy: White Marriage and Recovery (inscribed), 1984 (Box 8, Folder 265)
    - Gooch, Brad: The Daily News (inscribed), 1977 (Box 8, Folder 266)
    - Gooch, Brad: Jailbait and Other Stories, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 267)
    - Hartman/Slater (editors): Fresh Paint, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 268)
    - Jordan, Celia: Babies of Illinois (inscribed), 1985 (Box 8, Folder 269)
    - Krusoe, James: Jungle Girl (inscribed), 1982 (Box 8, Folder 270)
    - Lazzaro, Victor (illustrator): Poems: An Early Start Preschool Reader, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 271)
    - Myles, Eileen: Sappho's Boat (inscribed), 1982 (Box 8, Folder 272)
    - Notley, Alice: Phoebe Light, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 273)
    - Pearce, Celia: Mondays (inscribed), 1982 (Box 8, Folder 274)
    - Ricard, Rene: God with Revolver, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 275)
    - Rollins, Henry: 2-13-61, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 276)
    - Skelley, Jack: From Fear of Kathy Acker (inscribed), 1984 (Box 9, Folder 277)
    - Skelley, Jack: Monsters (inscribed), 1982 (Box 9, Folder 278)
    - Trinidad, David: Pavane (inscribed), 1981 (Box 9, Folder 279)
    - (author unknown): 1,000 Knock Knock Jokes for Kids, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 280)
  - Subseries B: Periodicals
    - The American Phonographer, January [1890's] (Box 9, Folder 281)
    - B City no. 3, Spring 1986 (Box 9, Folder 282)
    - BAM no. 481, 5 April 1996 (Box 9, Folder 283)
    - Barney no. 1, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 284)
    - Barney no. 3, Winter 1983 (Box 9, Folder 285)
    - Cafe Society no. 1, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 286)
    - Cuz no. 2, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 287)
    - Enclitic, vol. 8, nos 1 and 2, Spring/Fall 1984 (Box 9, Folder 288)
    - The End is Here, undated (Box 9, Folder 289)
    - Flat Disk Newsletter, vol. 4, no. 16, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 290)
    - Fonografic Star, January-July and October-December 1850 (Box 9, Folder 291)
    - G.Q., Vol. 53, no. 8 - article on L.A. poets p. 94, August 1983 (Box 9, Folder 292)
    - The Hollywood Kids, vol. 3, no. 38, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 293)
    - Little Caesar no. 11, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 294)
    - Magazine, vol. 13, no. 2, Spring 1983 (Box 9, Folder 295)
    - Magazine, vol. 13, no. 3, Summer 1983 (Box 9, Folder 296)
    - Magazine, vol. 14, no. 1, Winter 1983-1984 (Box 9, Folder 297)
    - Mirage #0, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 298)
    - Mormon Curiosity, [1983] (Box 9, Folder 299)
    - Night Voices no. 4, April-June 1981 (Box 9, Folder 300)
    - The Optimist, no. 21, September 1986 (Box 9, Folder 301)
    - Poetalk Poemphlet vol. 7, no. 11, and vol. 7, no. 12, May and June 1983 (Box 9, Folder 302)
    - Primary Writing no. 1 - Via Negativa by Jane DeLynn, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 303)
    - Santa Monica Review, vol. 1, no. 2, Spring 1989 (Box 9, Folder 304)
    - Santa Monica Review, vol. 2, no. 2, Spring 1990 (Box 9, Folder 305)
    - Santa Monica Review, vol. 3, no. 1, Fall 1990 (Box 9, Folder 306)
    - Santa Monica Review, vol. 3, no. 2, Spring 1991 (Box 9, Folder 307)
    - Seen Magazine, vol. 1, no. 1, Spring 1987 (Box 9, Folder 308)
    - Soundviews, no. 25, September/October 1993 (Box 9, Folder 309)
    - Soup, no. 2, [1981] (Box 9, Folder 310)
    - Soup, no. 4, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 311)
    - Upstart, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 312)
    - Artpaper vol. 8, no. 1, September 1988 (Box 11, Folder 324)
    - Artpaper vol. 8, no. 7, March 1989 (Box 11, Folder 325)
    - BAM no. 149, February 11, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 326)
    - Congula #10, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 327)
    - The Contemporary vol. 1, no. 1, November 1983 (Box 11, Folder 328)
    - Endless Party #8, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 329)
    - LACE vol. 2, no. 4, September/October 1987 (Box 11, Folder 330)
    - L.A. Reader, August 12, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 331)
    - Overture vol. 58, no. 8-includes article and photo of Ed Smith, November 1978 (Box 11, Folder 332)
    - Newspaper Clippings, 1983-1984, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 333)
    - Atopic Site, August 1996 (Box 11, Folder 334)
  - Subseries C: Art Show Catalogs
    - Security Pacific Bank: Contemporaries: 17 Artists, January-March 1980 (Box 9, Folder 313)
    - Security Pacific Collection: 1985-1987 Acquisitions (Box 9, Folder 314)
    - Security Pacific Gallery: Frames of Time and Context, January-March 1987 (Box 9, Folder 315)
    - Security Pacific Gallery: Art in the Public Eye, June-August 1989 (Box 9, Folder 316)
    - Offenes Kulturhaus: Relikte and Sedimente (Skip Arnold performance), 1993 (Box 9, Folder 317)
  - Subseries D: Miscellaneous Printed Materials
    - "Reflections on Our Friendship" - book-style greeting card, [1975] (Box 9, Folder 318)
    - MidAmericaCon Progress Report 4 - Program from Science Fiction Convention, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 319)
    - Catalog for Sun and Moon Press, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 320)
    - Pamphlet from Jack Kirby Birthday Party, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 321)
    - Playbill for show, "The World of Ray Bradbury," autographed by Bradbury, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 322)
    - Japanese comic book, [date unknown] (Box 9, Folder 323)